http://www.stardock.com/policies/privacy

Stardock.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Stardock.com This policy is also applicable to Stardock's other Web sites.
WE DO NOT SHARE YOUR EMAIL ADDRESSES OR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH ANY ORGANIZATION THAT IS NOT MAJORITY CONTROLLED BY STARDOCK CORPORATION.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This information is used to generate reports on the overall traffic to the site for bandwidth planning and usage statistics.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of items in your shopping cart. Stardock.net accounts on the various websites (like WinCustomize.com and for installing software via Stardock Central) also uses cookies as part of their validation process.
Do Not Track
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Website analytics
Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.
By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in Google's Privacy Policy - external site and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the opt-out service provided by Google - external site.
Our sites also transmits and uses Analytical data to and from other third parties such as Facebook, Amplitude, and Visual Website Optimizer. You can opt out of these by disabling or refusing cookies.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies (i.e. ONLY what they have access to from setting in your cookies). We do not allow advertisers to see any private information including email addresses, home addresses, phone numbers, or any other private information.
Registration Forms
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email) and demographic information (like their zip code and age).
Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
Order Forms
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code and age).
Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We may use this data in the future to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
Data Retention
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
We DO NOT store payment information after the transaction has taken place.
Surveys
Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like zip code or age).
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data in the future to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
Email
Stardock scans the text of e-mail messages in order to filter spam and detect viruses.
This process is completely automated and involves no humans.
The only exception includes requests by users that Wincustomize support staff access their email messages in order to diagnose problems; when Stardock is required by law to do so; and when we are compelled to view or disclose personal information because we reasonably believe it's necessary in order to protect the rights, property or safety of Stardock, its users and the public. Stardock only scans e-mail contents to provide you a reliable service. Stardock does not share or reveal e-mail content or personal information with third parties, other than in certain exceptions dictated by the law and common sense.
Stardock Activation
Some Stardock products require activation over the Internet to use their enhanced versions. Depending on if your order was directly through Stardock or through a third-party, we may ask for your first name, last name, email address, and the serial number/activation code for the product you have purchased.
Unique identifying information about your personal computer and/or network such as; IP address, MAC address, SID, Motherboard ID, hard disk ID, OS Version and number of activation attempts may also be collected and logged. There are reasonable limits on how often you can activate a given product to help deter piracy, but for most users, this limit will not be reached. If you have difficulties, please contact support@stardock.com. This information will not be used by third parties, but may be used by Stardock to contact you about updates or other Stardock-related news.
Stardock Entertainment's Online Services
Stardock's games collect information about the player from Steam and/or GoG such as the user's nickname, avatar, and Steam Id/GoG Id. This information is used to provide online functions like leaderboards, match making, and in-game stats related to the game that are displayed on our website. We will maintain your game activity history for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
Assessments (Hardware)
Stardock's TweakVista and Tweak7 products, at the request of the user, send generic information about the computer hardware under analysis to Stardock.
This data will not be provided to any third parties and will only be used to provide anonymous high level reports to other customers of TweakVista and Tweak7.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Stardock.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Credit card information for orders is secured via industry standard 128-bit SSL encryption.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us.
You can send email to info@stardock.com
You can visit the following URL: www.stardock.com/accounts/subscriptions
In addition, some products may prompt you for additional opt-in decisions during check out through our online store.  These questions will default to opting-out of additional promotional communications from our affiliates, however customers may choose to receive promotional e-mails at their discretion.
Data Quality/Access
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:
You can send email to support@stardock.com
Your Rights
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.
Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: support@stardock.com or by mail: 15090 Beck Rd, Plymouth, MI, 48170, United States
Stardock Sites
This policy is also applicable to Stardock's other Web sites, including but not limited to:
ashesofthesingularity.com
elementalgame.com
galciv.com
galciv1.com
galciv2.com
galciv3.com
joeuser.com
offworldgame.com
politicalmachine.com
sinsofasolarempire.com
sorcererking.com
wincustomize.com
Changes
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Last updated: 8/7/2019
Thank you! Please check your email for a confirmation link. Once confirmed, you can look forward to receiving exclusive specials and announcements direct from Stardock.
Need to unsubscribe?
